<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Diane Larlus&#39;s Personal Page</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Diane Larlus&#39;s Personal Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 18:48:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/</guid>
      <description>2021
 Paper accepted at 3DV21: NeuralDiff: Segmenting 3D objects that move in egocentric videos [paper, project page, video] Co-organizing the ImageNet Past, Present, Future workshop at NeurIPS20 Paper accepted at ICCV21: Concept Greneralization in visual representations [project page, video, code] I&amp;rsquo;m one of the organizers of the PAISS Summer School 2021 (organized by MIAI, PRAIRIE and NAVER LABS Europe) Invited talk at the Women in Computer Vision (WiCV) Workshop at CVPR21 [Video] Invited talk at the ANITI research institute (scientific seminar) 2 papers accepted at CVPR21  Probabilistic Embeddings for Cross-Modal Retrieval [paper, code] Continual Adaptation of Visual Representations via Domain Randomization and Meta-learning (oral) [paper, blog]   Area Chair for CVPR21, MVA21, ICCV21, BMVC21 2 papers accepted at WACV21  Unsupervised meta-domain adaptation for fashion retrieval [paper, code, video] StacMR: Scene-Text Aware Cross-Modal Retrieval [paper, code, video]    2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 18:48:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>NeuralDiff: Segmenting 3D objects that move in egocentric videos. Vadim Tschernezki, Diane Larlus, Andrea Vedaldi. 3DV 2021 Concept Greneralization in visual representations. Bülent Sariyildiz, Yannis Kalantidis, Diane Larlus, Karteek Alahari. ICCV 2021 [project page, video] Continual Adaptation of Visual Representations via Domain Randomization and Meta-learning. Riccardo Volpi, Diane Larlus, Gregory Rogez. CVPR 2021 [paper] Probabilistic Embeddings for Cross-Modal Retrieval. Sanghyuk Chun, Seong Joon Oh, Rafael Sampaio de Rezende, Yannis Kalantidis, Diane Larlus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent talks</title>
      <link>/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 18:48:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/</guid>
      <description>          June 2021   Invited talk at the Women in Computer Vision (WiCV) Workshop at CVPR21 - Lifelong visual representation learning [Video]   May 2021  Invited talk at the ANITI research institute (scientific seminar) - Learning from weak supervision and mitigating catastrophic forgetting   October 2020  Keynote Speaker for MIAI Days - Lifelong visual representation learning   August 2020  Invited talk at the ILR Workshop at ECCV20 - From Instance-Level to Semantic Image Retrieval [Video]   November 2019  Invited talk at the SOLARIS Workshop - Self-supervised learning for category-level geometry estimation   April 2019  Invited talk at the StatLearn 19 conference - Learning Image Representations for Efficient Visual Search   November 2018  Invited speaker, AI and Vision session at SophIA Summit - Visual Search   July 2018  Lecture at the PRAIRIE Artificial Intelligence summer school (PAISS) [slides] - Visual Search          Older: see CV    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 18:48:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/</guid>
      <description>          2021/2022   Comprendre des données visuelles à grande échelle - ENSIMAG, Grenoble   May 2021   Guest lecture on Visual Search - Hanoi University of Science and Technology (HUST), Vietnam   2020/2021   Comprendre des données visuelles à grande échelle - ENSIMAG, Grenoble   2020  Découvrir l’intelligence artificielle par le jeu (Discover AI with games is a 2 day training session for high school teachers) - Maison pour la Science Alpes-Dauphiné   Nov 2019   Lecture on Visual Search as part of the &amp;lsquo;Deep Learning&amp;rsquo; course for the MVA master - ENS Paris   2019/2020   Comprendre des données visuelles à grande échelle - ENSIMAG, Grenoble   Feb 2019  Lecture on Visual Search as part of the &amp;lsquo;Deep Learning in Practice&amp;rsquo; course for the MVA master - ENS Paris   2018/2019  Comprendre des données visuelles à grande échelle - ENSIMAG, Grenoble   July 2018  Lecture on Visual Search at the PRAIRIE Artificial Intelligence summer school (PAISS 2018) [slides]     Older: see CV    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>/older_news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/older_news/</guid>
      <description>2018
 Invited speaker, AI and Vision session at SophIA Summit 2018 Paper accepted at ECCV18: Semi-Convolutional Operators for Instance Segmentation [paper] Our work on Capturing the Geometry of Object Categories from Video Supervision has been accepted to TPAMI CVPR18 outstanding reviewer award Lecture about visual search at the PRAIRIE Artificial Intelligence summer school PAISS 2018 Paper accepted at CVPR18: Self-supervised Learning of Geometrically Stable Features Through Probabilistic Introspection (spotlight) [project page, video]  Back to the Main Page</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
