<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Diane Larlus&#39;s Personal Page</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Diane Larlus&#39;s Personal Page</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 18:48:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news/</guid>
      <description>2023
Doctoral Consortium chair for ICCV23 Area Chair for ICCV23 2022
Co-organizing the Self Supervised Learning: What is Next? workshop at ECCV22 Paper accepted at 3DV22: Neural Feature Fusion Fields: 3D Distillation of Self-Supervised 2D Image Representations [paper, project page, video] Keynote speaker at the joint CAp-RFIAP 2022 conference Paper accepted at ECCV22: Granularity-aware Adaptation for Image Retrieval over Multiple Retrieval Tasks [paper] Manuscript accepted to the TMLR journal: TLDR: Twin Learning for Dimensionality Reduction [paper,code] Invited talk at the O-DRUM workshop at CVPR22 Paper accepted at CVPR22: On the Road to Online Adaptation for Semantic Image Segmentation [paper, code and benchmark] 2 papers accepted at ICLR22 ARTEMIS: Attention-based Retrieval with Text-Explicit Matching and Implicit Similarity [paper] Learning Super-Features for Image Retrieval [paper,code] Co-organizing the Wiki-M3L workshop at ICLR22 Area Chair for CVPR22 2021</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 18:48:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>Granularity-aware Adaptation for Image Retrieval over Multiple Retrieval Tasks. Jon Almazan, Byungsoo Ko, Geonmo Gu, Diane Larlus, Yannis Kalantidis. ECCV22 └─ paper Neural Feature Fusion Fields: 3D Distillation of Self-Supervised 2D Image Representations. Vadim Tschernezki, Iro Laina, Diane Larlus, Andrea Vedaldi. 3DV22 └─ project page On the Road to Online Adaptation for Semantic Image Segmentation. Riccardo Volpi, Pau de Jorge, Diane Larlus, Gabriela Csurka. CVPR22 └─ project page &amp;ndash; code TLDR: Twin Learning for Dimensionality Reduction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent talks</title>
      <link>/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 18:48:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/</guid>
      <description> Sep 2022 Invited talk at the Thoth team at Inria - Towards Semantic Understanding in Egocentric Videos Sep 2022 Invited talk at the Linkmedia Speaks Science seminar series - Lifelong visual representation learning [Video] Jul 2022 Invited talk at the 1st International Workshop on Pervasive Artificial Intelligence - Lifelong visual representation learning Jul 2022 Keynote Speaker at CAp-RFIAP 2022 - Lifelong visual representation learning Jun 2022 Invited talk at the O-DRUM Workshop at CVPR22 - Using Text in Computer Vision Apr 2022 Invited talk at GDR TAL Day - Learning transferable visual representations Jan 2022 Invited talk at KUIS AI Meetings - Towards Semantic Understanding in Egocentric Videos Jun 2021 Invited talk at the Women in Computer Vision (WiCV) Workshop at CVPR21 - Lifelong visual representation learning [Video] May 2021 Invited talk at the ANITI research institute (scientific seminar) - Learning from weak supervision and mitigating catastrophic forgetting Oct 2020 Keynote Speaker for MIAI Days - Lifelong visual representation learning Aug 2020 Invited talk at the ILR Workshop at ECCV20 - From Instance-Level to Semantic Image Retrieval [Video] Nov 2019 Invited talk at the SOLARIS Workshop - Self-supervised learning for category-level geometry estimation Apr 2019 Invited talk at the StatLearn 19 conference - Learning Image Representations for Efficient Visual Search Nov 2018 Invited speaker, AI and Vision session at SophIA Summit - Visual Search Jul 2018 Lecture at the PRAIRIE Artificial Intelligence summer school (PAISS) [slides] - Visual Search Older: see CV </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jan 2021 18:48:42 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/</guid>
      <description> 2022/2023 L&amp;rsquo;apprentissage continu de représentations visuelles - ENSIMAG, Grenoble (webpage) Dec 2022 Lifelong visual representation learning - Master AI 4 One Health, UGA, Grenoble 2022 Découvrir l’IA par le jeu (Discover AI with games, a 2 day training session for high school teachers) - Maison pour la Science Alpes-Dauphiné Jan 2022 Guest lecture on Visual Search - Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology (PTIT), Vietnam 2021/2022 Comprendre des données visuelles à grande échelle - ENSIMAG, Grenoble Nov 2021 Lifelong visual representation learning - Master AI 4 One Health, UGA, Grenoble May 2021 Guest lecture on Visual Search - Hanoi University of Science and Technology (HUST), Vietnam 2020/2021 Comprendre des données visuelles à grande échelle - ENSIMAG, Grenoble 2020 Découvrir l’IA par le jeu (Discover AI with games, a 2 day training session for high school teachers) - Maison pour la Science Alpes-Dauphiné Nov 2019 Lecture on Visual Search as part of the &amp;lsquo;Deep Learning&amp;rsquo; course for the MVA master - ENS Paris 2019/2020 Comprendre des données visuelles à grande échelle - ENSIMAG, Grenoble Feb 2019 Lecture on Visual Search as part of the &amp;lsquo;Deep Learning in Practice&amp;rsquo; course for the MVA master - ENS Paris 2018/2019 Comprendre des données visuelles à grande échelle - ENSIMAG, Grenoble July 2018 Lecture on Visual Search at the PRAIRIE Artificial Intelligence summer school (PAISS 2018) [slides] Older: see CV </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>/older_news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/older_news/</guid>
      <description>2020
Best reviewer award at NeurIPS20 Keynote speaker at the MIAI DAY 2020 event Paper accepted at NeurIPS20: Hard negative mixing for contrastive learning [project page, video] Invited talk at the Instance-Level Recognition Workshop at ECCV20 [video] Paper accepted at ECCV20: Learning Visual Representations with Caption Annotations [project page, blog] Joined as Editor for International Journal of Computer Vision Industrial chair at ECCV20 Area Chair for ECCV20 and CVPR20 2019</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Older projects</title>
      <link>/older_projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/older_projects/</guid>
      <description>Back to the Main Page</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
